var title = 'Traduza para grego.';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "11",
   answer: ["έντεκα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "12",
   answer: ["δώδεκα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "13",
   answer: ["δεκατρία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "14",
   answer: ["δεκατέσσερα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "15",
   answer: ["δεκαπέντε", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "16",
   answer: ["δεκαέξι", "δεκάξι", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "17",
   answer: ["δεκαεφτά", "δεκαεπτά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "18",
   answer: ["δεκαοχτώ", "δεκαοκτώ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "19",
   answer: ["δεκαεννιά", "δεκαεννέα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "20",
   answer: ["είκοσι", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "30",
   answer: ["τριάντα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "40",
   answer: ["σαράντα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "50",
   answer: ["πενήντα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "60",
   answer: ["εξήντα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "70",
   answer: ["εβδομήντα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "80",
   answer: ["ογδόντα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "90",
   answer: ["ενενήντα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "100",
   answer: ["εκατό", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];